Advertise your product or brand here
contact www.OpenSubtitles.org today
Yes. Mr. Cho.
Yes. that's the place.
The warehouse where
we worked on the Japanese kid.
Yes. he's comfy and well.
He was a lot more gentle
than what you told me.
He wasn't trouble at all.
he took my lead well.
He was a bit cheeky though.
He's a funny guy.
How much was this guy worth
by the way?
Right? I knew he was loaded.
He's covered in designer goods.
He must be well off.
What?
Oh...
He must be rich.
Yes. I see.
We got proper merchandise
for once.
Almost here? I left the door open.
Come on right in.
I'll see...
Jerk. I was talking...
Mr. Cho's almost here.
Get out!
Get out now!
Shoot!
Damn it...
It's been a while. friend.
I told you
you would see me again soon.
You... wait...
It's just...
Oh yeah. I said
I would give you money.
I'll give it to you for real!
I'm not lying this time.
you'll get it. okay?
It's fine.
Friends shouldn't pay
each other money.
Don't kill me!
Please don't kill me!
Goddammit. what are you doing?!
You got blood on my shoe!
Idiot!
Jackass. it's this season's
brand-new model!
I barely managed to buy it
from the first batch!
I could just kill you!
Look at it.
I'm going to use this
to carve your heart out.
You know what?
Blunt instruments are more painful
than sharp knives.
You can't die quick with these.
How much is your client
paying you?
I'll pay you double...
Friend. you said we're friends!
Don't kill me. please!
Right. friend.
I told you.
I'm the last friend you'll meet
before you die.
It's nothing personal.
We're pros.
and this is just business.
(The Childe)
Nice work today Marco.
You promised me more
from this match onwards.
Hey Marco!
You eat well
and take care of
yourself with that money!
You know about the big match
next week. right?
I put a load of money on you!
Arrogant jerk...
Damn Kopino half-breed...!
Got your butt kicked this time?
Your opponent was a Thai?
Those Thais sure got
spicy punches.
Someone really did a number
on our mighty Marco's face.
Don't glare at me. idiot.
How's your mother?
She should really get
that surgery soon.
What brings you here today?
Because of your father?
Any news?
Nothing so far.
But hang in there.
If he's alive.
you might find him one day.
I wouldn't even be
looking for that man
if it wasn't for Mom's operation.
Come on now.
What's that?
Use it to hire someone in Korea
to look for him.
Hey! Hey!
Marco!
You're later than usual.
LaLiga's it's closed already
but Premier League
is still betting.
Which team has the highest odds?
Let's see...
Um. Burnley?
Yeah. it's Burnley.
They're going against Chelsea.
What are the odds?
250 to 1.
All on Burnley.
Hey Marco.
that's not a great idea.
Why don't you just buy
the lotto ticket?
You'll have a better
chance of winning.
I said all on Burnley.
Ay Gago.
It's on me. mate.
Long time no see Marco.
That last fight was sick. Huh?
Big shot Thai guy
didn't stand a chance.
Thanks to you
I made a pretty penny.
Um? Thanks for that.
Oh yeah. So ah...
how's searching for daddy going?
Any leads?
- Of course not...
- Why do you care?
But I do have a job
that might interest you.
I've had my eye on this
fancy jewelry store downtown.
I'm going to get to work on it...
You want in?
Come on. man.
All you have to do is
cut the power
and keep the security busy.
You don't even have to go in
and I'll give you 10%.
Store that size...
even with the middleman.
it'll be 100 big ones. easy.
10%. Marco.
What do you say?
- I'll think about it.
- Come on. man!
What's there to think about?
You know what.
I'll even forget
about mommy's medication.
(Chelsea 4:0)
(Yo. Chelsea took all your money.)
When you go around the back
to the building
you'll find the power box
and a guard booth.
Here.
They'll bust in as soon as you
keep the guards to busy
cut the power to the building.
No problem.
Get back jerks!
Hey! Are you okay?
Oh no. are you okay?
I didn't see you run out...
We should go to the hospital...
Why am I speaking Korean?
I'm really sorry.
We should go to
the hospital right away.
Korean?
- Are you Korean?
- What?
Well. not exactly.
How are you feeling?
All the tests came back well.
I told you this was unnecessary.
we could've settled last night.
what was the point of this?
Even so.
you just never know
about accidents.
There could be lasting effects.
This isn't much. please take it.
and I'm so sorry.
By the way. you speak
Korean really well.
You look like one too.
anyone will think
that you're a Korean.
I get that a lot.
Did you learn Korean somewhere?
Or are you...
what was it called? Kopino?
You are. right?
Sorry. I shouldn't have
said that...
Yeah?
What?
I was going to take your money.
but it stank
so badly of your sweat.
It would be proper to say
that they found us.
rather than us looking for them.
It means your father
did not forget about you.
As you know.
cases like this are so rare.
How many fathers
came looking for
their Kopino kids here?
None. zero.
They just plant their seeds and
get the hell out of here.
When is he coming?
Oh yeah. he's coming right away.
It looked like he was in a hurry.
And this is my gift to you.
It's a Korean calling card.
You might need it there.
so keep it with you.
What a stench.
Marco Han?
You're him.
Good to meet you.
Thank you.
(Law Firm The Royal Partner
Kang Won-seok)
Your father's a bit sick.
so I came instead.
Do you understand
what I just said?
I don't speak Tagalog at all.
but a little English.
would you prefer that?
It's okay. you can speak Korean.
You speak Korean so well.
Mom forced me to
speak Korean or English.
I had to go to a Korean school.
Korean school?
You need those to fly.
Passport. visa and such.
Isn't money great?
Anything is solvable with it.
Han. look here.
She's a hospice
who will look after your mother.
Because of your father's
condition.
we have to hurry.
Pack lightly and come out.
Right now?
Why? Is there a problem?
But...
For her sake. wouldn't it be best
to head out as soon as possible?
Paying for her surgery is
not even a bother to him.
He'll probably take care of it
right away.
It's a quick flight to Seoul.
Pack up quickly. okay?
He really wants to see you.
(Hokyung Foundation
Accused of Slush Fund...)
(Illegal Succession
at Hokyung Foundation...)
(Hokyung Foundation's Slush Fund.
Whistleblowers Missing...)
(Attorney Kang Won-seok)
Yes. Kang. how did it go?
Very good. that's great.
When's the flight?
Okay.
I'll have everyone on standby.
come here at once.
Okay. good.
So? how did it go?
Sir?
Thankfully. their editors
are quite amicable to us.
so we managed to
kill all articles.
Return for what?
We will be the main sponsor
for Daeil Daily's annual
corporation expo
for the next 3 years.
For the other 3 outlets.
we'll be the main ad client...
So pathetic...
It's so easy taking
someone else's money.
It's a sensitive period.
it'd be best not to get mixed up
with malicious tabloids.
I know.
Do I look like an idiot
who can't read the room?
That's not what I meant.
- Whatever.
- Sir?
- That'll be all.
- Yes. sir.
You haven't been here
in a long time.
Get some rest
and see you tomorrow.
That's all right. sir.
I'll head back to Seoul...
As you wish. sir.
There's someone
I want you to meet.
so let's have breakfast tomorrow.
Yes. sir.
This way.
So. father.
how are you holding up?
They're leaving the Philippines.
so just hang in there.
What did you say?
Yes. father. the youngest.
That youngest son you've been
waiting for is on the way.
Happy?
Are you?
Yes. that mutt.
Your mutt's on the way here.
Just hang on
until he arrives. okay?
We don't have time.
Have the cars on standby
so that we can leave immediately.
Understood. sir.
Man. I almost missed it.
I thought you'd leave tomorrow.
but returning on the same day?
They must really be in a hurry.
They're filthy rich.
putting you in business class?
Who am I?
A friend.
Consider me a friend for now.
Listen. friend.
You're heading to Korea.
do you even know why you're going?
What?
There's no way you would.
Oh yeah. isn't this
your first time in Korea?
Should I give you a tip?
This will help you out big time.
Once you're there.
use English whenever possible.
Koreans love
English speaking people.
Hey. this works. For sure.
One hundred percent.
And of course.
an American accent is the best.
Pretend like a 2nd.
or 3rd generation Korean-American.
Trust me.
They'll do whatever...
A British accent is okay too.
but Koreans aren't
really used to it.
So an American accent is the best.
works everytime.
Hey…
But don't use
a Southeast Asian accent.
Never. ever!
Better off not using it.
You have to be careful.
No point in tipping off
that you're a Kopino.
- Am I right?
- Who are you?
Like I said. an amigo. a friend.
I may be
the last friend in your life.
- What?
- By the way...
if we go by age.
I'm actually older.
I look young
but I got a few years on you.
So. you shouldn't swear
just because we're friends.
I really hate rude jerks.
What are you on about?
Who said I was going to
be your friend?
Life never works out
the way you intended. bud.
Your English pronunciation
is quite good.
What are you talking about!
Excuse me.
May I ask you
to return to your seat?
- Of course.
- Thank you.
Think about it.
Isn't it fishy?
Going to another country
on a plane
isn't like walking to a local bar.
It's not that simple.
Visa. passport. and all that.
It's weird. don't you think?
Should I tell you
why you're going to Korea?
I'm off.
See you soon.
Crazy ass...!
Yeah. we just touched down.
No. I'm on a delivery run.
Where are you?
Me? I'm in a business meeting.
Yeah.
How did you return so quickly
after the clean up?
Don't worry.
I did everything as per my order.
I cleaned it up nicely.
We were never there.
So my job's finished?
There's no end to our work.
- Is he the one?
- Yeah.
Put him inside.
Damn. my brother's hot.
Doesn't he look like a celebrity?
Take a look.
So similar. right?
Who?
Right. you don't watch TV.
Too bad. that guy's hot too.
Look at his muscles.
those are so dope.
Real dope.
Yeah?
So? What will you do?
Do what?
Just stick to the original order.
Okay.
By the way...
what about the favor I asked you?
I brought it.
but do you really need it?
You never know.
I'm preparing for the worst.
Better safe than sorry.
Don't worry. I practiced a lot.
Damn it.
I'm going to be late for school.
Yoon-ju. I have to go.
Thank you!
See you later!
It sure is stunning here.
Great water. great air...
Director Han. sir.
why are you doing this to me?
Director Han! What's going on?!
You are making a huge mistake!
You know who I am!
How will you handle
the backlash...
That's enough.
Please keep your mouths shut.
your breath stinks.
So. are you two well acquainted?
No need to play dumb.
You're not just well acquainted.
you gentlemen are
practically best friends.
Even so. this is plain nasty.
You hold great authority
and honor in this society.
Am I right. Mr. Publisher?
(Hokyung Foundation
Accused of Slush Fund...)
Illegal Succession
at Hokyung Foundation...
You have no problem
sucking others dry.
what are you?
A tick or a parasite?
This guy fed you this. right?
(Hokyung in Hot Waters
Over Slush Fund...)
I'm an impatient type.
could you answer right away?
Yes. yes!
How many years have you
worked with my father?
19 years? 20?
This is why I have
trust issues with humans.
You've swapped allegiance to Jang
after backstabbing my father?
Director Han. that's not it.
please listen to me.
Please. just this once.
I have to tell you something...
You think Jang will win?
Isn't that why you did this?
Director Han. please hear me out!
Please listen to me.
I got something to tell you...
You were here
when this was built. weren't you?
This is about
2.8 million square feet. right?
Cedar forest over there.
and there. what's that tree?
- Cypress tree. sir.
- Right. cypress tree.
And even more forests beyond that.
There's not a single soul
within a 10 km radius.
Aren't you curious?
These missing people.
where could they have gone?
(Hokyung Foundation's Slush Fund.
Whistleblowers Missing...)
Isn't that why you wrote it?
They're all here.
Director Han.
please don't kill me!
Please. don't kill me!
What? What?
Sensitive period. right?
Don't worry about your family.
I sent all those photos
to your families.
Every single one.
Not just to your wives.
but to all your children too.
So. don't you worry.
That's not all.
those are plastered
all over the internet.
So both of you have disappeared.
leaving behind a will.
No one will find you. right?
Why would anyone look for you.
after seeing these?
Untie him. right now!
Director Han. I'll do my best!
Sir. please!
Look at you.
For old times sake.
I'll give you a chance.
See that forest over there?
The cedar forest.
If you reach there.
I'll let you live.
Good? Let's run. are you ready?
One second! Hold on!
Run in a zigzag.
You'll have a lower chance
of getting shot.
- Thank you.
- What are you doing. get ready.
Start running on three.
I'll start shooting after 10.
Here we go.
One.
Two.
I said to run on three.
he couldn't listen
to save himself.
Dr. Lee. have you slept well?
Yes. thanks to you.
- Have you heard?
- Yes.
Everything is perfect. isn't it?
Please don't disappoint me
this time.
It's almost time.
please go prepare.
Kid. how old are you?
Punk. I just asked you a question.
How old are you. jerk?
Twenty-four.
Speak Korean.
I know you speak it.
What an idiot.
You don't even
understand the basics?
He said 24.
Oh. 24.
Learn basic English. will you?
Learning it won't kill you.
Sure.
So full of vitality.
a long way
from the expiration date.
Shut your damn mouth
and stick to driving!
Yes. sir.
What's that?
Why isn't he overtaking me
if he's so damn busy?
What the heck?
Increase speed.
What the hell for?
Buddy! Hey!
You sure drive like an idiot!
- Step on it! Now!
- Stop the car!
(Unknown Caller ID)
Who is this?
What?
So?
Who are you guys?
What?
How much?
Hey.
Get everyone on standby.
Marco!
Mercedes really is the bomb.
It's worth every penny.
Hey friend. good to see you.
I told you we'd see
each other soon.
There's a reason
why people go nuts over Mercedes.
If you get into an accident
like that
without seatbelts.
everyone should be dead.
Am I right?
Friend. are you scared?
There's no need to be.
relax. ease up.
What are you looking at?
Thinking of taking off?
That won't be easy.
Who are you?
Tell me.
I told you. a friend.
- A friend?
- Yes. that's right.
And this is...
my job.
Why are you doing this to me?
It's a bit tough
to explain everything
to you right now.
But don't worry.
You'll find out for yourself
when it's time for you to die.
What?
I told you in the airplane.
that you came here to die.
You're going there to die.
Stop talking nonsense. prick.
Prick... What?
Buddy! Where are you going?
He speaks Korean so well.
Hey! Buddy!
Stop! Hey!
It's a lot higher than I thought.
You okay?
Jerk. you got a death wish?
You prick!
Get over here. you prick!
Shut your mouth.
Lord...
Dammit!
Huh? Very nice. that's great.
Director. we found it.
Professional?
These idiots...
Father. looks like
we got a proper roadblock.
We got some hyenas around.
I don't know who these guys are.
but they're going all out.
Since you're down.
they think we're weak.
and ambushing us. these jerks.
He wants $10 million.
He wants $10 million
for that mutt.
It's all ready. sir.
Okay.
Just hang in there.
I'll go get that mutt myself.
(Law Firm The Royal Partner
Kang Won-seok)
Hello. this is Law Firm The Royal.
Please stay on the line.
we'll connect you right away.
(Call Forwarding)
- Hello?
Seriously?
That could've been terrible.
Where are you now?
Yes. I know where that is.
I'm on my way.
so stay right there.
Mr. Kim. it's Marco!
Where are you?
I'm getting calls
saying you disappeared!
Someone's trying to kill me.
Everyone I came with are all dead!
What the heck are you saying?
Have you contacted your father?
You punk.
Idiot.
Hey. friend!
Didn't I tell you
that I've never missed my targets?
This village is the only place
you could've run to from there.
it's too obvious!
I knew you would be making
a call from the payphone!
How did I know?
I'm a professional.
An expert.
Stop. that's enough.
I said stop.
If you continue
being uncooperative.
I could just shoot you dead.
No need
to raise your hands though.
Right. he boxed...
Damn it...
He has a mean punch.
A proper hit could have killed me.
Hop in!
Man. oh. man...
It's a brand new car!
Damn it...
What's going on?
What is happening here?
It's exactly as you see it.
So. do you remember me?
Are you okay?
I didn't see you run out...
Kopino?
You are. right?
Who are you?
Who are you people?
Don't rush it.
you'll find out before you die.
What?
This will be fun.
What is the matter with him?
Turn it around! Now!
Why are they together?
Go after them!
Where are we going?
To your father.
You came to Korea to see him.
no?
The one following us
is your brother.
He's the one
who ordered us to bring you in.
Speak of the devil.
What do you think you're doing?
Are you messing with me?
I don't really have the time
to mess around with you.
What?
Then what are you doing right now?
Doing what?
I'm carrying out my work.
Have you forgotten
my order of bringing that mutt?
Go nag Mr. Kang about it.
You ordered him. not me.
What?
I've told you
several times already.
we may share the office.
but we're separate entities.
Are you insa...
Are you so desperate to die?
If you got the chops.
give it your best shot.
Hello? Hello?
That wench!
Catch up to them.
Hold on tight.
Stay on them! Go!
Turn it around. idiot!
That wench. let's move!
Catch up! Floor it!
Freaking idiots.
do they know how to drive?
What a hassle.
Who's that in the Mercedes?
Holy crap. I almost died!
Jesus Christ...
Where did she go?
I'm asking you. jerk!
Where is she?
He's pretty good.
What about my father?
I thought we were going to him.
Your father?
He's nearby.
In this land
of beautiful mountain.
water and air.
he's got maybe a day or two.
What's with that face?
Kang didn't tell you?
You father. Chairman Han is dying.
Bad heart. I hear.
Did you know
he is the chairman of
Seoul's biggest foundation?
Hokyung Foundation built many
colleges in and around Seoul.
tons of hospitals too.
It's a huge foundation.
You didn't know it was that big?
I bet you thought
your father had a bit of money.
If it stopped right here.
you'd be the luckiest kid.
That's too bad. right?
He wouldn't have looked for you
if it stopped right here.
Your brother and your father are
in a bit of a rush.
If your father dies.
your brother will
lose the foundation
to his half-sister.
When the chairman was
in and out of consciousness.
his wife Jang got his will. seal.
and vocal confirmation.
So. your brother has to
keep him alive
- no matter what.
- What the hell is this?
I don't believe this...
That's why you're here.
do you understand?
I don't...
The man you call your father
has a really bad heart.
Your father and your brother
need this.
They need your heart.
You get it now?
What? Got more questions?
Me? I received the opposite order.
Wow. not bad at all.
Just stick to the original order.
Here or there.
your fate is to die.
Think of it
as clocking out slightly early.
What the heck!
You prick!
My damn car!
I'm going to kill her!
That's enough.
You messed up my car royally.
Damn it...
Stop running. it's hot.
I'm your big brother...
I'm happy to meet you.
My brother...
Come in. come in.
Think of this place
as your own home. okay?
But why are you so dirty?
Let's go upstairs. come.
Do you like the place?
Follow me.
Oh my. Ga-young.
when did you get here?
What a good kid.
you heard
it's father's surgery day
and got here just in time.
She's a good daughter.
You really have your ways.
You finally found this mutt.
Of course.
watch your mouth though.
This is a matter of
our father's life and death.
Have you ever seen me fail?
Never. you're just that good.
Males in this household
don't do anything for my life.
You look like death.
Little sis.
if you need some allowance
from me.
you and your mommy
should be nice to me.
Damn wench.
Like mother. like daughter.
Try to understand her.
Our little sister
was always a pain.
Never mind that.
shall we go meet our father?
Let's go.
Father. your little boy is here.
Damn it...
Your call cannot be connected...
(Recent Calls)
So? What does it feel like
to see him?
He's much too old
for you and Ga-young
to call him father.
More like grandfather.
Come here.
This will be
the first and last time.
all men in our family
get together.
let's take a selfie
to commemorate.
Smile. jerk. come on!
Smile!
That looks good.
What are you all doing?
Let's get started.
What? You looked for father.
So why?
Not your type?
Be a good son.
How long will this take?
Dr. Lee says it will be
about 9 hours.
We don't know what they're up to.
so put more men outside.
Yes. sir.
Marco!
The donor is conscious!
What? How is that possible?
Did you anesthetize him properly?
- Do it again!
- Yes. doctor!
- Do it quickly!
- Yes...
Doctor!
Check on the chairman first!
What?
Get up. you awake?
It's me. friend.
Are you happy to see me?
We don't have a lot of time.
Could you snap out of it
One. two. three!
You punk.
Don't run around naked.
put this on.
These punks...
Are you
really my father?
How...
How could a father ask his son
to give up his heart
to live?
How could a father do that?
If this is what you wanted...
you shouldn't have looked for me!
We don't have much time.
wrap it up.
I have had it...
That mutt cannot die.
- got that?
- Yes. sir!
Move out of the way!
Buddy!
Do you hear me?
Damn it. answer me!
Answer me if you do. jerk!
Yeah. yeah. yeah. I hear you
very well! Speak!
What's with
that piss-ass English?
- Just speak Korean. an idiot.
- Piss-ass...
I don't know who you are.
but let's come to an agreement.
Are you the one
who asked for $10 million? Huh?
I am. prick!
What will you do now?
What else?
Walk out of here.
We'll go out that door proudly.
Take the lead.
Never seen him before.
Give me a calculator.
1. 10. 100. 1.000...
Do you even know
how much $10 million is
in Korean won?
Of course.
At this morning's exchange rate.
it's 11.8575 billion won.
Very precise.
That is an incredible
amount of money.
It's tough
to get that kind of money
exchanged so quickly.
Don't worry. I can wait.
I got a lot of time today.
Okay. very well.
I'll meet you half way
at $5 million.
Isn't that enough for that mutt?
Do you want half of
this mutt's heart then?
$10 million.
- You're hard to bargain with.
- Firm price.
You could really
screw yourself over.
Don't worry. I can handle myself.
That prick...
All right. $7 million.
not a penny more. got it?
No. $10 million.
Front sight between rear sight...
My offer is more than fair!
Pull back the hammer.
Pull the trigger.
Stop! Stop shooting!
Are you out of
your goddamn minds?
That damn wench. is she nuts?
You idiots.
I told you not to shoot!
What's this?
Get in there
and assess the situation!
Damn. I got hit...
No way.
It really hit me.
I can't get $10 million
if he dies.
I was just saying.
don't look at me like that.
Seriously?
Bring the doctors back.
do you hear me?
Director Han. sir...
Friend. stay alert.
What? You jerks!
You prick...
Easy. easy. calm down.
why are you all worked up?
Your old man won't die right away.
And you guys are the ones
who shot at him.
not me.
What the heck are you doing?
So?
Thanks to you.
time's running out.
You little...
$10 million? You poor ass.
Yeah. $10 million. you rich ass.
Cayman Islands or Virgin Islands?
What?
Secret US dollar accounts
you stashed away.
We did our homework.
Whichever is easier. which one?
- Caymans.
- Okay.
Here. show your brother this.
Send it here right away.
Give me my phone.
It's me.
send $10 million
to an account I tell you.
Yes. right away!
$10 million! In USD!
Are you deaf?
United States dollar!
What?
Purpose?
I made that account
so that I don't have to report it!
It's my goddamn money!
You punk!
Give me another phone.
The screen's off. puck. tap on it.
It's me.
(Deposit Information: $10.000.000)
Happy. jerk?
Put that gun down
and hand over the mutt.
Okay. very well.
that was the deal.
Take him.
Move. get a move on!
Move. out of the way.
Father! You can't die!
Get him to the doctors now!
What?
Get over here. you idiot.
Take him away!
Yo. friend!
Cheer up.
You're not dying today.
Don't worry. just trust me.
I'll be off then.
Damn it...
I got hit in the leg...
I'll put your money to good use.
Think of it as doing a good deed.
Yo. poor ass. stop.
What is it?
Killing me won't get you
back your money.
I know. jerk.
I'll consider it
as the cost of doing business.
Why then?
It's rather embarrassing.
A rumor could get out
that I got robbed
by a bunch of nobodies.
That's how the world works.
One conversation leads to another.
and I'll be a laughing stock.
Why don't you think it over?
Being embarrassed
would be a better option.
Than being dead.
So full of it until the end.
Jerk. can't you read the room?
I have said it many times.
I'm a professional.
What? Professional?
Get down!
Get down on the floor!
Die.
Prick.
You jerk.
Easy. easy...
Professional...
Indeed.
You live hard for a poor ass.
Is your flight coming up soon?
I'm too messed up to walk you out.
Oh yeah. I...
Damn it. I forgot about this.
This hurts.
It hurts so much.
I completely forgot about it.
It's all over. so let's go home.
Don't worry about him.
he's got nothing to do with you.
Let's just go.
Hold me softly. jerk.
You saw who I am. right?
That hurts. easy...
Wait. wait...
Come out.
I can see your shadow.
What the heck?
This isn't even funny.
Do you see this?
I'll let it slide this time.
just move aside. okay?
You can go. I don't need you.
The game's over. missy.
Your father's fortune's all yours.
that must be nice.
Congratulations. good.
Go have a party with your mom.
and move aside.
We're busy.
You boys took me for a fool?
Was I that obvious?
What if that mutt comes back
and changes his story?
Saying he's part of this family.
or spilling the beans
about what happened today.
What if he blackmails us later?
What a headache.
Why? Did I sting you in the feels?
No. no...
You prick.
Do I look like a panhandler?
I won't take your dirty money
even if you fed it to me. got it?
You're a nobody.
Do you expect me to believe you?
I would rather trust my dog.
And you!
What? Me? Really?
You called me?
How much? I'll hire you.
How much do you want to
get rid of this mutt?
Under the circumstances.
the minimum fee is...
What the hell am I saying?
Why are all offsprings
of this family
so messed up?
Is it the blood?
Consider yourself lucky
that you didn't get that blood.
Don't make that face
like it's a big revelation.
I told you just a moment ago.
You got nothing to do
with these people.
You know most of the fixers
in the Philippines. right?
Find a kid for me.
it's a rush job.
The client could die
in a day or two.
Just find him.
then you'll get a fat check.
Say what?
Get me a decent guy.
You need money to save this place
and build a school.
But even so...
If this place disappears.
what'll happen to them?
Will you let them
roam the alleys as we did?
Those jerks want a child's heart
so they can live.
What's your hang up?
That's why you need to get me
a mentally tough and smart guy.
By the way...
Don't you trust me?
What's with you?
I'm a professional.
I got a decent reputation
in my line of work.
You know that.
Also.
let me do something good
before I die.
Are you okay?
(St. Lucian Medical Center.
Philippines)
It's me.
Do you have the medical report?
You jerk!
Hey. easy. easy.
Sorry. friend.
It was tough.
but we got a happy ending.
Your mom's surgery is included
in the $10 million.
It's better than
robbing a jewelry shop. isn't it?
Are you listening to
your own nonsense?
Aren't you happy that a jerk
like him isn't your dad?
You jerk!
You thought
I would let you hit me again?
Throwing punches left and right
because you boxed a bit?
What the hell do you know?
What do you know!
Of course. I do. idiot.
I'm a Kopino too.
What?
What? What. man?
Did you see it?
If you did.
stop being a drama queen.
What's with that look?
Forget it. let's just go.
If you got something to say.
say it on the way.
we got a flight.
My damn leg...
Not leaving?
Cops will be here soon.
go with your friend.
No wonder. no resemblance at all.
Blood never lies.
Hey! Don't ever come back!
Got that? You poor asses.
She's calling you. answer her.
It hurts so much. damn it!
It hurts...
That wench really did
a number on my car.
I'm going to get a trypophobia
looking at this.
Wait a minute. bullet holes aren't
covered by the insurance.
Can you get a move on?
You were so fast
when running away.
Does it have to rain too?
You can drive. right?
My leg hurts too much to drive.
you do it.
Put on your seatbelt. punk.
Can you drive well?
No. go a little further.
What are you doing?
Hey. hey. go easy.
You drive like yourself.
Go. We can go now.
Who taught you to drive?
(Kim's Kopino Children's Home
Construction Site)
I heard the surgery went well.
Mr. Kim told me.
Oh yeah. will you continue to
look for your father in Korea?
Do you want my help?
You know I'm a professional!
I can give you
a special discount for the job...
Sorry.
Forget it.
Father or not.
I'm so sick of Korea.
Very well.
But when you have some time.
go visit there...
Have you gone to the hospital?
I can't go to hospitals like that.
I got somewhere else.
Expensive.
but he's a skilled doctor.
I feel better with these.
Stopped the bleeding.
and the symptoms died down.
I just came to see your face
one last time.
You won't see me
even if you wanted to.
Now that you got some money.
live a happy life with your mom.
And stop with the boxing match.
got it?
My friend.
Friend my ass.
Jerk...
"Jerk"?
Did you just call me a jerk?
I don't have a lot of time.
You cold-blooded kid.
I really don't have a lot of time!
Wait for me. punk!
(The Childe)
(Kim Seon-ho)
(Kang Tae-ju)
(Kim Kang-woo)
(Ko Ara)
(Directed by Park Hoon-jeong)
It's strange.
I keep on gaining weight.
I always want to eat.
I sleep well...
Before.
I did like what. 50 pull-ups?
But now.
I can easily do a hundred.
And everyone keeps telling me.
"You look better.
you look healthy."
That's exactly what I'm saying...
There's nothing wrong with you.
Nothing at all.
Absolutely healthy.
You are in great. great condition.
You obviously take
good care of yourself.
Some people can experience
similar things
when they stop smoking
after smoking a pack a day
for almost 10 years.
So this is?
Vitamins.
Multi-vitamins.
They're good for you.
So in the future.
don't go to any illegal clinics
without permits.
It's not like medical licenses
can be bought.
What the heck.
Do you want subtitles for any video?
-=[ ai.OpenSubtitles.com ]=-